http://www.aeronix.com/privacy/

Loading...
Home
Products
Products Top Categories:
Introduction
We at Aeronix, Inc. are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.
Aeronix, Inc. has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
What Personally Identifiable Information May Be Collected?
Aeronix is a small business with specialized products and services not of interest to the general consumer. When a visitor requests product information or requests to be contacted, Aeronix may collect the following information:
Name
E-mail Address
Company Name/Title/Address
Phone Number
Reason for Contact
IP Address
A visitor must provide check box consent for each such transaction when such information is requested.
If you choose to have a relationship with Aeronix, Inc., such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.
How is the information used?
Aeronix uses this information solely to facilitate the business relationship with the requesting person/organization. Aeronix does not sell this information to a third party, nor will it otherwise share the information without specific consent of the information provider.
Where is the information stored?
Data submitted to the Aeronix web site is encrypted with 256bit SSL secure certificate, and the web site data is stored in a secured database. Similarly, Aeronix network drives are secure. Aeronix will take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure to protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
Children's Privacy
The Aeronix web site is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.
Commitment
We are committed to privacy and are actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Aeronix, Inc.'s Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands.
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@aeronix.com. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.
Menu
Home
Products
Services
News/Events
Working at Aeronix
Current Opportunities
Aeronix Customers
What are you looking for?
Go
CLOSE
